Hello, nice to meet you.
Why are you smiling?
Oh, we're not supposed
to smile?
I'm new at this funeral thing,
I don't know how it works.
-What should I do?
-You must look sad.
No... Not that sad.
It depends on how long
you know the deceased.
Yeah, I didn't know him.
And I know very few people here.
Then just look serious.
Something between serious
and mournful.
No, wait.
Breath.
Bend down a little
and shake your head.
Then say something like:
"He was so young..."
-He was so young.
-Look, that's his son.
Greet him.
-Ah, his son?
-Yes.
Brother.
Hi, man.
Congratulations.
Congratulations?
That's not it?
Thanks. Thank you very much?
What a joy!
Greetings, I miss you.
"I miss you", right?
-"My condolences."
-You too, my friend.
Thank you.
Sorry I didn't get you anything.
I was in such a hurry
that I didn't even bring you
a little something.
-Why are you laughing?
-No. I'm not laughing.
He was so young...
So young...
When is the speech?
Will the father
of our guest of honor speak?
-What's your name, man?
-Manuel.
Look, Manuel,
the guest of honor is dead.
He's right here.
Fuck! Is this a casket?
All the time I was touching a...
Oh, no!
Was it contagious?
I don't wanna die
of mortal stuff.
I thought this was the table
for the food...
There won't be dessert, right?
I have a suggestion
for those who set up this... event:
you could tell people
to have lunch beforehand,
since there's nothing to eat.
Me, for example.
I didn't eat and I'm starving now.
That's rude. One more question.
This... This little doll is him?
What? No, man. Don't come here.
He was already dead
when I came here.
Yeah. No.
They didn't even offer me a beer.
I'm telling you.
No food and no drinks.
I'm telling you. Yes?
What? Did I hear "circumcision"?
Oh, "appendicitis"? What is it?
An appendicitis party?
We gotta go there.
There are no chicks here, man.
Yeah, right.
Okay.
We're stopping by Roy's, right?
That's better. Great.
Are you picking him up?
Me? Okay.
See you later, champ! Monster!